When you had that 310-yard drive,
were you just like, "Ooh, I think I'm in
good hands."
>> why I kept pulling driver and just
shanking it cuz I'm just going to go for
it. And that's like Kellen's motto and
he's just going to hit it straight, so
probably it was a He used a better
strategy, but I mean, it was fun, man.
It was It was a blast. Tyler, how close
do you follow, obviously, the draft in a
couple of days?
I mean, we're going to watch it, for
sure, pretty closely. Um
you know, I've been here the whole time
and seen, you know, all the guys come
in. It's just the excitement around it,
but you know, also we're fired up to be
back. Um the guys that we have in the
building are looking really good, so you
know, my job is to keep getting better
and whenever we get the new rookies in,
it's just to get everybody up to speed
and and we'll How How much do you become
a fan, like googling these guys, reading
about these guys, knowing, you know,
maybe what needs are versus like what
could be actually good?
I mean, to to be honest, I trust the the
the front office completely. I'm not
super well-versed in the, you know, DN
or interior D-line play or a lot of
those guys or what, you know, what makes
them, you know, I want to find out what
makes those guys tick and and be a part
of this this Saints organization and and
what kind of culture we're trying to
bring and I I think with last year's
rookie class and what the what Kellen
and the staff is building is we want the
right guys and guys who love to work
hard and and want to be a part of the
New Orleans Saints, so I trust him. I'm
just I'm exactly like you guys. I'm
excited to find out. What's the vibe
been like in the building with everybody
kind of coming back to the start of the
program? It's been great energy. It's
been great. I think Ted does an
unbelievable job and the whole strength
staff, so and nothing all the trainers.
So, everybody's I think obviously it's
I'm going into my second year, but
talking to a lot of the guys, the amount
of people that are in the building that
have stayed in New Orleans and I wanted
to make sure that was a a priority, but
it's fun. I think the biggest thing is
when we're when we're working, we're
working and and it's been showing so
far, so it's
Tyler, it's no secret the Saints have
done a lot of homework on receivers. I
mean, are you
more than just curiosity? I mean, have
you really like dove in and tried to
watch some of these guys that might go
in the top 10? Yeah, I've I've watched
um almost all of their their film from
college and um just obviously curiosity
and I think all of those guys have
have a lead level play. I think that's
the biggest thing, at least from what
I've seen.
All over the draft board, I think
there's a lot of talent, so
I think at the same time we got guys
that De'Vante Harris and Jalen Polk I've
been throwing with this whole offseason
who are studs. I mean, they're they're
studs, man, and and Ceedy has been
working the whole time with me in this
well, so
I'm I'm really excited to to kind of get
the the ground running with those guys
and then obviously, if we get somebody,
that'd be great, but if not, we're we
feel really great about it and
I know the staff and and everybody's
feeling great. We're going to play in
the playoffs. I can't remember now if
you're really familiar with, obviously,
Chris Olave.
How pumped would you be to get reunited
with him and
what do you think he would bring to New
Orleans if the Saints ended up selecting
him? Yeah, I mean, he's one of my one of
my close friends. Obviously, my guy and
he brings a level of physicality, I
think, for any team that's that's really
hard to replicate and
I think it obviously would be it would
be great, for sure.
I know I'm fired up to be back here
right now and
I mean, the the wide receivers that we
do have that we've signed so far,
it's it's exciting to see those guys
work, too. You spoke about it before,
but like doing this McMillan Hondo Fest,
uh Banana Ball, like you've been very
involved this offseason, obviously,
while also having a kid. How important
is that aspect for you to like continue
to be visible to this community? I I
just want I want to be in New Orleans. I
mean, I feel like
there's so much stuff going on that's
like I'm not like trying to like, you
know, go to everything. I'm just like
cuz New Orleans is the best place. It's
the best time of year. I've been telling
everybody January to April is like there
every weekend there's a festival,
there's stuff going on. You want to be a
part of the community and I I was
obviously super intentional about just
making relationships that way, but I
want to do it and have fun, be a part of
everybody and and and knowing that
football season comes around, you know,
as as players, there's not much time to
go experience New Orleans, so it's it's
been probably one of my favorite times
of year to to be out there with
everybody,
but knowing that, you know, we're back
now and we want to keep grinding. Tyler,
what about
Yeah,
I don't know. I almost almost said no
almost said no this. I was like, "Oh,
man, this would be this would be a lot
of fun cuz I've been playing any golf,
but I was like, "We'll just We'll have
some fun with it." But You won? Yeah, I
know. I was I didn't really want to par
for one, but
I'm I'm excited to be part of his team
and but yeah, I mean,
like I said, there's so much stuff going
on here at the Saints.
That's why I love it, honestly, because
like everybody just comes together and
has fun and has a good time, so
and then it kind of leads you into the
Saints season, so Tyler, what about the
times we've I know it's been a year ago
at this time it was almost I think twice
as bad like the shooting, nobody knew
what was going on. Now, you're basically
almost facing the franchise, you're at
all this stuff. Can you think about what
the next year may be like and the
responsibility that comes with
continuing that trajectory? I'm going to
keep the same mindset. You know, I think
a lot of
I mean, last year there's so much
unknown, there's a lot of talk about,
you know, everything, but for me, I want
to keep getting better. I only played
nine games and
I'm going to do everything I can on and
off the field to try and be here for a
long time, but knowing that
I have so much more to learn. I haven't
really done anything yet, but I know
how I operate, how I want to be as a a
person and player and I'm a
you know, lead with my best foot forward
and
and and surround I'm I think the guys in
the locker room has been the the coolest
thing. I was talking to to David Andrews
today. He's like, "It seems like
everybody's like really close with each
other."
And it's like the second the second day
and I was like, "Man, it's You're
exactly right. Everyone Everyone hangs
out, you know, we're all excited to be
here, so and I want to I want to be the
the guy that can kind of ignite that
Tyler, what a What is the experience
a couple You know, like last year you
were training for the combine, you don't
know where you're going to go. You get
dropped in in the A.
This year you
get nine games to show what you can do,
everybody knows what you can do. Now you
can kind of
take a deep breath, relax Yeah, I think
the the sense of urgency, you know,
having a having a development plan of of
being in the office for the full year,
knowing what I want to continue to work
on, knowing what we can kind of focus on
going forward, what we can kind of clean
up. And for me, that's that's the
exciting part is now you
gotten your feet wet, so to speak. You
know, I think you're coming into the NFL
and you have, you know, all these guys
and
a lot of leaders that we've kind of lost
and actually through the business and
but being able to step up and try and do
everything I can in my own right to be
that guy and
but still, like I said, we have
you know, everyone that it's going to
take to to to get it done and and know
that it's going to be a long long road,
but you know, we're here for it. Tyler,
everything you're doing this offseason
What What about the times we've seen
where you've gotten together with
whatever teammates are here locally,
high school fields and stuff? Is that Is
that something you arrange, somebody
else, a veteran local player arrange?
And why is it important to you to do
that when you can? No, I mean, I've I've
I've tried to get as much guys here as
possible and I think that's, like I was
saying before, the exciting part is
everyone's been,
you know, here working. You know, J
Polk, Olave, you know, De'Vante, Juwan's
been here the whole time, you know,
Malik so I've been throwing with with
our Saints receivers for for the entire
offseason and and Ceedy included as
well, so
I feel like we haven't really, you know,
missed a beat and now heading, you know,
OTAs and minicamp, like I said, the
standard is now set, so we got to
continue to elevate it and and it's I
think that's the biggest part is, you
know, you go train somewhere else for a
lot of guys, but being able to be in New
Orleans and be with, you know, your
teammates, it's been really fun. And
then what else have you tried to carve
out as a routine for yourself? I mean,
are you constantly talking to coaches?
Are you Are you in the film rooms like
trying to like work off what you did
last season and
>> Yeah, we're not able to We can't really
meet with coaches specifically.
You know, yeah, but I've been, you know,
obviously, I watched every single game
from last year and and
put up together cut-ups of just stuff
that I can kind of work on.
Just, you know, timing out deep balls,
but every time I'm working on working up
in the pocket, you know, some of my
under center footwork. Really trying to
be intentional about that where I think
some some bigger plays can be had or
just managing it better that way, so
that's been the
the good part and also the stuff that
kind of drives you to keep getting
better. And you mentioned David Edwards.
Was that a good start [clears throat] to
free agency when you had a
left guard and a running back within the
first 3 hours of I was fired up. I was
fired up just cuz
I mean, getting to got getting to know
who he is as a person and who he's
played with in his career, the the
quarterbacks he's played with.
I mean, he's such an elite level player,
but now, you know, we're locker mates
now and he, you know, him, you know,
choosing to be next to me in the locker
room, it's it's really it's really cool
deal and I can't wait to continue to
work with him cuz he's a beast. There
have been a couple of prospects from the
tape that said like they want to play
with you specifically. What does that
mean to you and then also that you were
able to show last year? Like how much do
you think it is a reflection of that
then
what you guys have been able to do?
Yeah.
I mean,
I feel like we haven't been able to show
everything that we've been been able to
do and or want to do. And I obviously to
get that, you know, some of that
recognition from some of those guys and
that are obviously really good players,
elite level talent, so it's it's a it's
an honor, but knowing that, you know,
we have so much more and
I know I have so much more to grow, so
I'm
obviously, I I want to keep doing
everything I can and to get some of
those guys would be really good. A guy
like Chris Olave, like are our coaches
or front office people coming up to you
and asking you about specifically or are
you going to them? Yeah, for for sure. I
mean, there's I mean, I obviously got to
play with him and they have, you know, I
got I have the ins- you know, the inside
information about who he is and I
obviously who he is as a player and
it's all great things. I think that's
the the benefit of it and
and but we'll see. I think, you know,
whoever we get,
like I said, I trust I trust all the
front office and the coaching staff
because I think this point, you know,
they have a plan about what we're trying
to get done.
You going to Jazz Fest at all?
I'm going to try to. I I I got to see I
got to see how the baby's feeling on
that specific day, but I want to go see
maybe Tyler Childers or T-Pain would be
would be pretty cool, too.
I didn't get to go last year. I I was
like, "I just got here." And like Jazz
Fest was having a thing.
They just played jazz or what is
And And was like, "Oh, this is a
festival." So
I wanted to It's on the bucket list, so
I'm going to try and make it. How's
fatherhood treating you? It's good. He
just had his first full night of sleep
like 3 nights ago, so
he's feeling outstanding in his in the
workouts, and it translated today, but
uh
it's been good.